A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Secretary's Office, Biographical Files, RG 15 FA1280
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Staff, A-Z, 1951-1960; 2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
  - Flaster, Ann S. (Box 33)
  - French, Elizabeth A. (Box 33)
  - Galland, Helen (Box 33)
  - Galler, Barbara R. (Box 33)
  - Garvey, Judith Anne (Box 33)
  - Gazeley, Marjorie (Box 33)
  - Gilpin, Bettie B. (Box 33)
  - Glenn, Joanne O. (Box 33)
  - Greenhouse, Anne B. (Box 33)
  - Greve, Lois M. (Box 33)
  - Gustafson, Barbara B. (Box 33)
  - Haddock, Carol (Box 33)
  - Hanssen, Barbara J. (Box 33)
  - Harper, Walter (Box 33)
  - Harris, Charlene L. (Box 33)
  - Hart, Consuelo Elizabeth (Box 33)
  - Heizman, Barbara (Box 33)
  - Hegemen, Eileen (Box 33)
  - Hindsley, Anna (Box 33)
  - Hoffman, Burton R. (Box 33)
  - Hoffman, Kathleen (Box 33)
  - Hoisington, Corrine (Box 33)
  - Holden, Alice E. (Box 33)
  - Holland, Isabelle C. (Box 33)
  - Horton, Elizabeth B. (Box 33)
  - Howe, Elizabeth (Box 33)
  - Huffman, Margaret (Box 33)
  - Huisking, Claire (Box 33)
  - Hummel, C. Mary (Box 33)
  - Hunt, Louise W. (Box 33)
  - Hunter, Arthur D. (Box 33)
  - Hussey, Loretto (Box 33)
  - Jacques, Elizabeth M. (Box 33)
  - Janko, Dorothy (Box 33)
  - Johnson, Iris Yates (Box 33)
  - Johnson, Luther H., Jr. (Box 33)
  - Jones, Frances Guyer (Box 33)
  - Jones, Robert (Box 33)
  - Jones, Roosevelt (Box 33)
  - Kagen, Ruth L. (Box 34)
  - Kalman, Wendy (Box 34)
  - Kaplan, Marian A. (Box 34)
  - Katz, Leonard (Box 34)
  - Katz, Marjorie P. (Box 34)
  - Keen, Jane T. (Box 34)
  - Keenan, Laura M. (Box 34)
  - Keiler, Hella I. (Box 34)
  - Kellner, Bennett (Box 34)
  - Kern, Joan (Box 34)
  - Kissel, Victoria M. (Box 34)
  - Kransberg, Deborah (Box 34)
  - Laboy, Edward (Box 34)
  - Lally, Joan M. (Box 34)
  - Lane, Violet C. (Box 34)
  - Laurencin, Maurice W. (Box 34)
  - Lea, Leonard N. (Box 34)
  - Leaf, Louise S. (Box 34)
  - Leddy, Marilyn (Box 34)
  - Levin, Jenny (Box 34)
  - Lienhardt, Robert C. (Box 34)
  - Linnell-French, Phyllis (Box 34)
  - Loprete, Marilyn A. (Box 34)
  - Martin, Thomas T. (Box 34)
  - Mayers, Edith C. (Box 34)
  - Mays, Bibiana N. (Box 34)
  - McCluskey, Maureen E. (Box 34)
  - McGinty, Madeline K. (Box 34)
  - McLellan, Claire (Box 34)
  - McMahon, Kathleen E. (Box 34)
  - McMullin, M. Jean (Box 34)
  - McThenia, M. Amanda (Box 34)
  - Mead, Pauline A. (Box 34)
  - Megna, Mary E. (Box 34)
  - Meissinger, Maria F. (Box 34)
  - Merrill, Mary E. (Box 34)
  - Miller, Ann D. (Box 34)
  - Miller, Barbara A. (Box 34)
  - Miller, Charlotte (Box 34)
  - Minnis, Joan B. (Box 34)
  - Minton, Claire L. (Box 34)
  - Mitchell, Charlene Haupt (Box 34)
  - Morgan, Anne (Box 34)
  - Nagorski, Barbara (Box 34)
  - Nesbitt, Joan T. (Box 34)
  - Newman, Eva (Box 34)
  - Nichols, Ellen Joseph (Box 34)
  - Obluck, Gloria (Box 34)
  - Olin, Elizabeth S. (Box 34)
  - Omansky, Betsey G. (Box 34)
  - Operer, Madelon (Box 34)
  - Pattillo, Daniel M. (Box 34)
  - Pawelczyk, Beatrice B. (Box 34)
  - Peery, Virginia S. (Box 34)
  - Preasha, James (Box 34)
  - Prettyman, Virginia (Box 34)
  - Price, Barbara A. (Box 34)
  - Quigley, Frances B. (Box 34)
  - Quinn, Judith (Box 34)
  - Ragan, Marian (Box 34)
  - Rankin, George (Box 34)
  - Ravenel, Katharine (Box 34)
  - Ricci, Adriana G. (Box 34)
  - Rossig, Louise (Box 34)
  - Rutherford, William (Box 34)
  - Sadue, Katheryn H. (Box 34)
  - Salerni, Richard (Box 34)
  - Salerno, Bernard (Box 34)
  - Sangren, Irene (Box 34)
  - Schneider, Elsa L. (Box 34)
  - Schumsky, Charlene G. (Box 34)
  - Schwartzman, Barbara (Box 34)
  - Sevin, Richard M. (Box 34)
  - Shearer, Cecile (Box 34)
  - Siddall, Doris E. (Box 34)
  - Siegmund, Joanne (Box 34)
  - Silverman, Charles (Box 34)
  - Silverstein, Diane B. (Box 34)
  - Simmons, Joan M. (Box 34)
  - Singer, Elna Campbell (Box 34)
  - Sinnott, Barbara T. (Box 34)
  - Skinner, Dorothy J. (Box 34)
  - Snodgrass, Roxana (Box 34)
  - Speier, Helen (Box 34)
  - Spiegel, Frimi (Box 34)
  - Sprout, Sarah (Box 34)
  - Stanton, Peter (Box 34)
  - Steinthal, Winifred (Box 34)
  - Stevens, Lois (Box 34)
  - Stollmeyer, Elizabeth (Box 34)
  - Stone, Winifred (Box 34)
  - Strom, Marie-Anne (Box 34)
  - Taylor, Julie (Box 34)
  - Thompson, Hilma (Box 34)
  - Trowbridge, M. Laird (Box 34)
  - Truitt, Francis (Box 34)
  - Tunison, Barbara (Box 34)
  - Usui, Elsie (Box 34)
  - Wagner, Carol (Box 34)
  - Wald, Gilbert (Box 34)
  - Waldeck, Doris (Box 34)
  - Wallace, Betty (Box 34)
  - Warwich, Virginia H. (Box 34)
  - Washington, Edward (Box 34)
  - Weber, Johanna (Box 34)
  - Weser, Deborah (Box 34)
  - Wiley, Carol J. (Box 34)
  - Williamson, Barbara S. (Box 34)
  - Wilson, Cynthia (Box 34)
  - Wilson, Rowan (Box 34)
  - Wolfe, Sarah M. (Box 34)
  - Wolff, Margaret J. (Box 34)
  - Wormser, Ellen (Box 34)
  - Wynn, William Earl (Box 34)
  - Yates, William (Box 34)
- Staff, A-Z, 1958-1971; 3; 9.2 Cubic Feet 7 record storage boxes
  - Abrams, Dianne, 1967 May 26 (Box 35)
  - Abrams, Jacqueline, 1966 May 31 (Box 35)
  - Aharon, Ruth, 1968 April 12 (Box 35)
  - Akin, Susan, 1968 April 5 (Box 35)
  - Alavosius, Carolyn, 1966 September 16 (Box 35)
  - Albertis, Loretta, 1968 September 6 (Box 35)
  - Alch, Catherine, 1961 January 13 (Box 35)
  - Alonso, Jose, 1971 October 15 (Box 35)
  - Amato, Jacqueline, 1960 December 30 (Box 35)
  - Ambrosoni, Margaret, 1971 May 31 (Box 35)
  - Amico, Marion, 1971 May 11 (Box 35)
  - Amirian, Elena S., 1961 July 28 (Box 35)
  - Amstutz, Patricia, 1961 February 28 (Box 35)
  - Amodeo, Rosemary, 1969 October 3 (Box 35)
  - Anderson, Barbara, 1966 December 16 (Box 35)
  - Anderson, Karen, 1967 August 31 (Box 35)
  - Anderson, Patricia, 1964 January 15 (Box 35)
  - Anderson, Alice, 1969 January 30 (Box 35)
  - Anish, Michele, 1968 August 30 (Box 35)
  - Apple, Elizabeth McGuire, 1967 January 12 (Box 35)
  - Arrota, Helena, 1970 November 30 (Box 35)
  - Atwood, Elizabeth Ann, 1967 January 31 (Box 35)
  - Aupperle, Charlotte, 1965 June 30 (Box 35)
  - Austin, Donna, 1964 July 31 (Box 35)
  - Austin, Robin, 1964 October 13 (Box 35)
  - Bachman, Joyce, 1970 January 30 (Box 35)
  - Backus, Diana, 1967 May 19 (Box 35)
  - Badgero, Nancy, 1967 May 5 (Box 35)
  - Baer, Martha, 1967 December 21 (Box 35)
  - Baerga, E. Jean, 1967 September 5 (Box 35)
  - Baker, Hazel (Nee Bradley), 1967 October 31 (Box 35)
  - Bakter, Stuart, 1968 January 22 (Box 35)
  - Baldassare, Patricia, 1966 July 8 (Box 35)
  - Barnard, Henry K., 1964 January 7 (Box 35)
  - Barrett, Nancy M., 1970 March 23 (Box 35)
  - Barry, Constance, 1961 January 31 (Box 35)
  - Battaglia, Algos, 1971 September 6 (Box 35)
  - Battelle, Jacqueline, 1966 September 16 (Box 35)
  - Beard, Linda, 1970 November 13 (Box 35)
  - Beddoe, Elizabeth, 1962 April 27 (Box 35)
  - Beddow, Gloria M., 1964 June 12 (Box 35)
  - Bell, James, 1964 August 28 (Box 35)
  - Bellows, Roberta, 1966 September 22 (Box 35)
  - Benson, James, 1967 June 6 (Box 35)
  - Baer, Alice, 1964 September 7 (Box 35)
  - Berg, Barbara Ann, 1964 February 28 (Box 35)
  - Bernstein, Howard, 1962 September 28 (Box 35)
  - Bertuch, Ruth H., 1964 July 24 (Box 35)
  - Beverett, Clayton, 1969 July 7 (Box 35)
  - Biedermann, Cathryn, 1969 September 1 (Box 35)
  - Biringer, Kathleen, 1970 August 14 (Box 35)
  - Black, Mary F., 1969 September 1 (Box 35)
  - Blackman, Joel, 1963 September 6 (Box 35)
  - Blackwell, Clegg, 1961 June 16 (Box 35)
  - Blanton, Mary Jane, 1962 February 22 (Box 35)
  - Blattspieler, Terri, 1970 September 25 (Box 35)
  - Bleier, Karen, 1966 August 17 (Box 35)
  - Boccaccio, Mary, 1971 December 31 (Box 35)
  - Boek, Edith, 1968 January 12 (Box 35)
  - Boeke, Richard, 1967 July 28 (Box 35)
  - Bogardus, Carol Parker, 1968 May 10 (Box 35)
  - Boody, David, 1970 October 2 (Box 35)
  - Bookoff, Estelle, 1965 November 15 (Box 35)
  - Bornemann, Toni Marie, 1964 July 24 (Box 35)
  - Bougerie, Nancy S., 1964 October 30 (Box 35)
  - Boyce, Frederick, 1963 May 3 (Box 35)
  - Boyd, Carol, 1967 February 24 (Box 35)
  - Bracey, Ronnie, 1969 April 25 (Box 35)
  - Bradley, Lynne, 1969 July 18 (Box 35)
  - Brady, Carolyn, 1964 September 4 (Box 35)
  - Brady, Marion E., 1964 October 20 (Box 35)
  - Bravman, Leslie, 1961 December 29 (Box 35)
  - Bremer, Toby, 1964 August 21 (Box 35)
  - Brennan, Alice, 1971 February 19 (Box 35)
  - Brett, Anne, 1970 January 30 (Box 35)
  - Brewer, Robert A., 1961 September 13 (Box 35)
  - Brickner, Pearila, 1970 January 7 (Box 35)
  - Bridges, James A., 1962 March 14 (Box 35)
  - Broderick, Beatrice, 1971 July 27 (Box 35)
  - Brooks, Ruth, 1964 February 3 (Box 35)
  - Brown, William A. (Box 35)
  - Bru, Georgina Ann, 1968 March 21 (Box 35)
  - Budzanoski, Marilyn Kay, 1970 September 4 (Box 35)
  - Bullwinkel, Margeret F., 1963 July 9 (Box 35)
  - Burnstein, Nancy, 1970 May 22 (Box 35)
  - Bush, Mary H., 1970 May 8 (Box 35)
  - Bussey, Charles A., 1965 November 22 (Box 35)
  - Butterworth, Carroll B., 1967 January 13 (Box 35)
  - Byrne, Daniel, 1964 March 30 (Box 35)
  - Byrne, Terrence, 1961 December 1 (Box 35)
  - Calabro, Diane, 1965 July 23 (Box 35)
  - Calenberg, Constance, 1961 February 2 (Box 35)
  - Calhoun, Judith L., 1968 August 23 (Box 35)
  - Cambrelen, Jaime A., 1966 January 11 (Box 35)
  - Cameron, Bertha, 1968 August 30 (Box 35)
  - Caminiti, June, 1970 September 10 (Box 35)
  - Canaday, Katherine O., 1962 July 20 (Box 35)
  - Cardiff, Ethel, 1966 August 31 (Box 35)
  - Carroll, Rush, 1968 September 20 (Box 35)
  - Casalaina, Maria, 1967 June 30 (Box 35)
  - Cave, Denise A., 1967 January 27 (Box 35)
  - Celentano, Kathleen, 1964 October 9 (Box 35)
  - Chacon, Luis, 1971 April 15 (Box 35)
  - Chapkines, George, 1968 March 19 (Box 35)
  - Charity, Suzanne, 1970 October 15 (Box 35)
  - Charney, Miriam R., 1960 April 30 (Box 35)
  - Chase, Beth, 1969 January 3 (Box 35)
  - Chenkin, Shura, 1969 September 11 (Box 35)
  - Chernek, Eleanor, 1970 May 15 (Box 35)
  - Christensen, Mary C. (Lukasik), 1963 February 11 (Box 35)
  - Cicero, Theresa, 1969 September 23 (Box 35)
  - Ciezkowski, Marion, 1968 May 31 (Box 35)
  - Cisler, Harry, 1965 August 20 (Box 35)
  - Citron, Allen, 1969 January 31 (Box 35)
  - Clark, Ann, 1968 July 12 (Box 35)
  - Cleary, Noreen, 1962 September 6 (Box 35)
  - Clucas, Nancy, 1970 August 28 (Box 35)
  - Codispoti, Joseph A., 1963 November 29 (Box 36)
  - Coerver, Lucinda, 1962 March 30 (Box 36)
  - Cohen, Geraldine, 1970 November 13 (Box 36)
  - Cohen, Sandra H., 1961 July 21 (Box 36)
  - Cole, Barbara W. (Nee: Lawrence), 1963 June 21 (Box 36)
  - Collins, Walter M., 1965 November 5 (Box 36)
  - Conrad, Edward, 1965 June 11 (Box 36)
  - Convey, Maryanne, 1963 June 28 (Box 36)
  - Coogan, Garth P., 1960 March 31 (Box 36)
  - Copeman, Christina, 1968 July 31 (Box 36)
  - Corboy, Catharine Ann, 1966 August 19 (Box 36)
  - Cornelius, Suzanne, 1970 August 28 (Box 36)
  - Cote, Paul, 1967 May 12 (Box 36)
  - Coulton, Catherine, 1968 February 22 (Box 36)
  - Cruz, Wilfredo, 1969 September 12 (Box 36)
  - Cuccia, Frederick J., 1966 August 26 (Box 36)
  - Cuccia, Krystyn, 1968 March 29 (Box 36)
  - Cummings, Roberta, 1962 September 14 (Box 36)
  - Curry, Valary, 1966 September 23 (Box 36)
  - Czajkowska, Theresa, 1970 November 20 (Box 36)
  - Dalmus, Ellen S., 1967 July 18 (Box 36)
  - Daniel, Phyllis B., 1968 December 31 (Box 36)
  - Daren, Hazel R., 1970 January 16 (Box 36)
  - Darvin, Iris, 1967 September 15 (Box 36)
  - Davanzo, Rosalie, 1964 January 24 (Box 36)
  - Davies, Patricia, 1961 January 27 (Box 36)
  - Davis, Samuel J., 1970 February 27 (Box 36)
  - Deery, Ann, 1969 January 31 (Box 36)
  - DeGennaro, Paula T., 1968 August 23 (Box 36)
  - DeRosa, Elizabeth, 1968 June 5 (Box 36)
  - Desmond, Abigail L., 1962 July 27 (Box 36)
  - Deutsch, Mazine B., 1967 January 31 (Box 36)
  - Diaz, Mario, 1968 June 14 (Box 36)
  - Dichtl, Sonja I., 1964 July 17 (Box 36)
  - Diggs, Julian, 1963 August 23 (Box 36)
  - Dinella, Ruth A., 1962 March 30 (Box 36)
  - Diskint, Harvey Ann, 1965 December 17 (Box 36)
  - Dolan, Carrie K., 1961 March 31 (Box 36)
  - Dolnansky, Ellen, 1968 August 30 (Box 36)
  - Dorr, Anne Marie, 1967 December 8 (Box 36)
  - Dowdell, Michael C., 1969 April 4 (Box 36)
  - Dowling, Mary Virginia, 1967 February 3 (Box 36)
  - Downs, Violet Marie, 1962 July 31 (Box 36)
  - Dreyer, Catherine M., 1962 August 31 (Box 36)
  - Driben, Adrienne M., 1963 June 28 (Box 36)
  - Druplas, Alma, 1966 April 29 (Box 36)
  - Dugan, Edna R., 1970 September 15 (Box 36)
  - Duncan, Mary K., 1970 April 17 (Box 36)
  - Dunleavey, Margaret A., 1965 October 29 (Box 36)
  - Durso, Paulette, 1971 January 15 (Box 36)
  - Dyson, Gerald R., 1968 March 15 (Box 36)
  - Eaton, Claudia, 1969 September 19 (Box 36)
  - Egan, Margaret M., 1968 April 12 (Box 36)
  - Ehrman, Judith, 1968 September 20 (Box 36)
  - Ellis, E. Gaynor, 1968 June 28 (Box 36)
  - Encaknacion, Theresa, 1969 May 29 (Box 36)
  - Eng, Barry, 1971 August 31 (Box 36)
  - Eng, Moon, 1964 October 20 (Box 36)
  - Engelsrath, Edna D., 1965 September 2 (Box 36)
  - Enstrom, Maxine K., 1964 August 14 (Box 36)
  - Eppse, Vincent, 1969 August 29 (Box 36)
  - Erwin, Jeanne S., 1970 August 28 (Box 36)
  - Estook, Helen B., 1967 February 27 (Box 36)
  - Evans, Sandra, 1969 August 22 (Box 36)
  - Ewing, Virginia (Timbes), 1971 July 23 (Box 36)
  - Fabrikant, Elizabeth, 1961 June 30 (Box 36)
  - Faeder, Helen, 1966 May 31 (Box 36)
  - Falvey, Catherine, 1961 September 29 (Box 36)
  - Fatt, Naomi, 1967 September 1 (Box 36)
  - Feldman, Nancy, 1964 August 14 (Box 36)
  - Ferguson, E. Rae, 1967 March 13 (Box 36)
  - Ferguson, Thomas W., 1962 June 28 (Box 36)
  - Field, Wanda, 1966 June 15 (Box 36)
  - Fife, Eugene, 1964 January 15 (Box 36)
  - Finch, Larry, 1971 July 30 (Box 36)
  - Fish, Jennifer, 1963 November 15 (Box 36)
  - Fitzgerald, Marilyn, 1971 April 15 (Box 36)
  - Fleischman, Charles W., 1963 August 30 (Box 36)
  - Fleming, Janice A., 1967 November 17 (Box 36)
  - Fontes, Karen, 1969 May 15 (Box 36)
  - Ford, Virginia K. (Mrs. Malachuk), 1966 September 28 (Box 36)
  - Frank, Elizabeth T., 1965 September 24 (Box 36)
  - Franson, Inegard, 1969 June 30 (Box 36)
  - Fraser, Ricardo, 1969 February 7 (Box 36)
  - Frazer, Jane B., 1965 November 24 (Box 36)
  - Frederick, Carole B., 1969 November 14 (Box 36)
  - French, Beverly, 1969 December 31 (Box 36)
  - Friedlander, Mary, 1966 July 19 (Box 36)
  - Friedman, Ellen G., 1965 October 15 (Box 36)
  - Gagliardi, Ralph M., 1966 May 27 (Box 36)
  - Galgano, Edward, 1969 September 5 (Box 36)
  - Gallagher, Gail A., 1961 March 20 (Box 36)
  - Gamble, Jennifer T., 1971 December 24 (Box 36)
  - Garland, Ellen L., 1961 December 29 (Box 36)
  - Garry, Marion, 1971 October 15 (Box 36)
  - Gatchalian, Raoul R., 1966 December 9 (Box 36)
  - Gawlinski, Caroline A., 1967 March 31 (Box 36)
  - George, Veverly B., 1961 June 16 (Box 36)
  - Gerstenzang, Joan, 1969 February 14 (Box 36)
  - Gia, Quinto, Linda, 1967 April 20 (Box 36)
  - Gibson, Sherman D., 1968 May 31 (Box 36)
  - Gilbert, Evelyn G., 1966 September 30 (Box 36)
  - Gillespie, Ann, 1969 February 26 (Box 36)
  - Giraldi, Louise M., 1967 May 30 (Box 36)
  - Gitelson, Susan A., 1964 September 18 (Box 36)
  - Gitt, Marcia, 1971 February 5 (Box 36)
  - Gluck, Joyce, 1961 May 12 (Box 36)
  - Goker, Filiz, 1962 February 6 (Box 36)
  - Goldwasser, Noreen, 1971 December 30 (Box 36)
  - Gonzales, Rogelio, 1968 September 20 (Box 36)
  - Grabelsky, Laura B., 1968 June 14 (Box 37)
  - Graham, Sarah S., 1961 June 15 (Box 37)
  - Grand, Vivian, 1961 February 10 (Box 37)
  - Green, Richard P., 1965 June 20 (Box 37)
  - Greenberg, Diane, 1968 August 30 (Box 37)
  - Greene, Carolyn E., 1968 September 6 (Box 37)
  - Greene, Jo, 1967 June 2 (Box 37)
  - Greene, Linda, 1970 January 23 (Box 37)
  - Greer, Margaret, 1966 September 2 (Box 37)
  - Griener, Arlene, 1970 April 17 (Box 37)
  - Grice, Audre D., 1970 June 30 (Box 37)
  - Griffing, Barbara, 1966 June 17 (Box 37)
  - Grobe, Pauline R., 1964 August 20 (Box 37)
  - Grossman, Carol V., 1961 August 23 (Box 37)
  - Grumette, Judith, 1969 May 30 (Box 37)
  - Gunner, Diane, 1964 January 31 (Box 37)
  - Haas, Mary Ann, 1970 February 27 (Box 37)
  - Habib, Carolyn Ann, 1966 August 12 (Box 37)
  - Hadden, Barbara, 1967 November 13 (Box 37)
  - Hait, Wendy M., 1967 September 8 (Box 37)
  - Hambsch, Diana M., 1970 August 28 (Box 37)
  - Hampson, Hugh, 1968 April 19 (Box 37)
  - Hanna, Olivia, 1970 January 19 (Box 37)
  - Hanning, Mary S., 1968 June 7 (Box 37)
  - Hardman, Ann, 1966 May 31 (Box 37)
  - Harnan, Susan G., 1965 November 12 (Box 37)
  - Harrington, Robert, 1961 June 13 (Box 37)
  - Harris, Edward B., 1964 July 23 (Box 37)
  - Harrison, Samuel, 1971 March 31 (Box 37)
  - Hartung, Susan C., 1963 January 11 (Box 37)
  - Hartwig, Jane, 1969 August 1 (Box 37)
  - Haworth, Lorna, 1971 May 14 (Box 37)
  - Hawryluk, Alexandra, 1969 June 6 (Box 37)
  - Hawthorne, Judith, 1970 August 28 (Box 37)
  - Heckman, Rosemary, 1963 May 10 (Box 37)
  - Hedrick, Lawrence, 1970 July 17 (Box 37)
  - Heifetz, Joan, 1961 August 18 (Box 37)
  - Heitman, Betty, 1964 June 30 (Box 37)
  - Heller, Marilyn L., 1961 June 30 (Box 37)
  - Heller, Virginia, 1964 February 28 (Box 37)
  - Hendler, Randolph, 1968 August 16 (Box 37)
  - Henkles, Elizabeth, 1965 September 3 (Box 37)
  - Henry, Catherine, 1964 May 29 (Box 37)
  - Herman, Eleanor, 1964 September 22 (Box 37)
  - Hernandez, Neftali, 1970 March 31 (Box 37)
  - Hess, Carol, 1963 December 31 (Box 37)
  - Hewitt, Vivian D., 1963 February 15 (Box 37)
  - Higgins, Nancy, 1969 June 13 (Box 37)
  - Hill, Roger, 1969 January 27 (Box 37)
  - Hinaekian, Juliette, 1963 August 16 (Box 37)
  - Hirsch, Jerry, 1966 September 9 (Box 37)
  - Hirsch, Michael, 1965 September 3 (Box 37)
  - Holbrook, Deborah, 1962 November 23 (Box 37)
  - Hoodes, Karen, 1965 May 31 (Box 37)
  - Horton, Mary Ellen, 1961 August 15 (Box 37)
  - Hurrell, Audrey, 1963 May 31 (Box 37)
  - Hutcherson, Nancy, 1966 February 28 (Box 37)
  - Iafolla, Aldo, 1968 September 12 (Box 37)
  - Intenzo, Carol, 1966 January 31 (Box 37)
  - Iovino, Diana, 1967 June 13 (Box 37)
  - Iaacson, Karen, 1967 July 14 (Box 37)
  - Jackson, Barbara, 1967 August 25 (Box 37)
  - Jeanty, Frantz, 1967 June 20 (Box 37)
  - Jenkins, Allean, 1971 October 29 (Box 37)
  - Jenkins, Edith, 1964 September 22 (Box 37)
  - Jenkins, Shirley, 1964 September 4 (Box 37)
  - Jenness, David, 1964 September 4 (Box 37)
  - Jensen, Joan, 1968 September 20 (Box 37)
  - Johnen, Petra, 1968 June 28 (Box 37)
  - Johns, Iaene, 1962 February 16 (Box 37)
  - Johnson, MargieLee, 1963 March 29 (Box 37)
  - Johach, Arlene, 1968 February 29 (Box 37)
  - Jones, Barbara E., 1961 September 8 (Box 37)
  - Jones, Delcina R., 1971 May 31 (Box 37)
  - Jones, Frances, 1961 July 31 (Box 37)
  - Jones, Shirley, 1970 March 13 (Box 37)
  - Joseph, Richard A., 1963 September 6 (Box 37)
  - Jurgenson, James, 1967 March 31 (Box 37)
  - Kalugerovich, Mary S., 1963 May 3 (Box 37)
  - Kane, Rebecca, 1967 December 15 (Box 37)
  - Kaplan, Leah, 1967 June 30 (Box 37)
  - Kaplan, Marina, 1970 September 24 (Box 37)
  - KaPoor, Catherine, 1971 December 31 (Box 37)
  - Karpevych, Christine, 1963 May 24 (Box 37)
  - Kaufman, Jerome, 1961 April 24 (Box 37)
  - Kaufman, Vivian E., 1964 November 13 (Box 37)
  - Kea, Shirley, 1969 August 15 (Box 37)
  - Keeperman, Emma, 1964 May 22 (Box 37)
  - Keiser, Elissa, 1967 October 13 (Box 37)
  - Kelly, Katherine, 1967 July 24 (Box 37)
  - Kelly, Ruth D., 1967 February 17 (Box 37)
  - Kidd, Candiss S., 1968 May 31 (Box 37)
  - King, Margaret T., 1966 November 4 (Box 37)
  - Kinney, Marjorie, 1963 August 30 (Box 37)
  - Kishiyama, Shirley, 1967 September 15 (Box 37)
  - Kissane, Teresa M., 1970 August 7 (Box 37)
  - Klahn, Robert, 1972 March 3 (Box 37)
  - Klein, Enid R., 1964 June 30 (Box 37)
  - Klein, Joan Ann, 1968 July 26 (Box 37)
  - Knowled, Gail, 1970 June 30 (Box 37)
  - Konechy, Sophia, 1964 February 28 (Box 37)
  - Kossin, Susan, 1971 August 13 (Box 37)
  - Kowsky, Claire M., 1968 November 30 (Box 37)
  - Kramer, Jean A., 1966 August 31 (Box 38)
  - Kreisler, Nancy H., 1966 January 21 (Box 38)
  - Krell, Rita I., 1962 September 15 (Box 38)
  - Krum, Gladys M., 1964 August 28 (Box 38)
  - Kulbaba, Jeanette, 1969 January 24 (Box 38)
  - Kunigonis, Ruth F., 1970 April 10 (Box 38)
  - Kurland, Judith, 1963 September 3 (Box 38)
  - Kurs, Mitchell, 1971 August 20 (Box 38)
  - Lambert, Barbara, 1965 July 16 (Box 38)
  - Lamkin, Beatrice, 1962 August 29 (Box 38)
  - Lanckton, Alison D., 1963 January 25 (Box 38)
  - Land, Barbara, 1962 May 16 (Box 38)
  - Landwehr, Joel, 1966 May 20 (Box 38)
  - Lane, Judith A., 1964 August 14 (Box 38)
  - Lasciak, Annette, 1966 September 30 (Box 38)
  - Lautmann, Margit, 1968 June 26 (Box 38)
  - Lawrence, Donna, 1969 August 7 (Box 38)
  - Lawson, Anne E., 1968 May 10 (Box 38)
  - Leavitt, Judith Louise, 1965 November 1 (Box 38)
  - Leberfeld, Laraine R., 1966 September 9 (Box 38)
  - Lecour, Bernice, 1964 June 10 (Box 38)
  - Lee, Nancy, 1963 June 28 (Box 38)
  - Lee Gant, Joan, 1969 September 1 (Box 38)
  - Lehman, Elena Maria, 1966 September 21 (Box 38)
  - Leising, Mary L., 1964 July 3 (Box 38)
  - Lem, Rose Lee, 1966 April 15 (Box 38)
  - Lemaire, Ingrid, 1971 December 31 (Box 38)
  - LeMonier, Karen, 1969 January 17 (Box 38)
  - Leslie, Ellen, 1970 September 14 (Box 38)
  - Levey, Mary, 1969 March 21 (Box 38)
  - Levy, Thomas G., 1963 July 26 (Box 38)
  - Lewald, Eric A., 1971 August 9 (Box 38)
  - Lewin, Irene, 1965 June 25 (Box 38)
  - Lewis, Solus Bill, 1967 December 29 (Box 38)
  - Liebman, Jo W., 1961 June 30 (Box 38)
  - Lieneck, Nancy, 1969 August 22 (Box 38)
  - Lilly, Sidney, 1969 December 10 (Box 38)
  - LoCascio, Emilia A., 1971 September 6 (Box 38)
  - Loder, Robin, 1968 June 14 (Box 38)
  - Logan, Henry J., 1965 February 10 (Box 38)
  - Loizeaux, Anne, 1968 June 7 (Box 38)
  - Lombardi, Cheryl A., 1968 April 5 (Box 38)
  - Lopez, Marvin J., 1964 May 12 (Box 38)
  - Lunn, Sharon A., 1967 August 25 (Box 38)
  - Lynaugh, Frances, 1964 June 30 (Box 38)
  - Lyons, Eleanor, 1966 May 24 (Box 38)
  - MacDonald, Judith, 1964 February 7 (Box 38)
  - MacFate, Alyce, 1966 August 25 (Box 38)
  - MacKinnon, Helen B., 1966 July 8 (Box 38)
  - Machuca, Felix, 1969 January 15 (Box 38)
  - Madsen, Kathleen, 1970 June 13 (Box 38)
  - Magee, Beryl C., 1961 June 30 (Box 38)
  - Magee, Ellen, 1971 July 30 (Box 38)
  - Mahon, Julianne M., 1963 July 31 (Box 38)
  - Malaspina, Anita, 1964 July 10 (Box 38)
  - Malcom, Judith W., 1962 September 12 (Box 38)
  - Mandernack, Gretchen M., 1965 June 25 (Box 38)
  - Mann, Martha H. (Bethea), 1967 June 9 (Box 38)
  - Marchant, Lucia D., 1968 February 9 (Box 38)
  - Marks, James, 1969 September 12 (Box 38)
  - Marler, E. Ruth, 1962 January 5 (Box 38)
  - Marquis, Sue, 1961 January 20 (Box 38)
  - Martelly, Frantz, 1971 March 31 (Box 38)
  - Martens, Jan J., 1970 September 18 (Box 38)
  - Martin, Joanne, 1967 September 8 (Box 38)
  - Martin, William, 1964 November 25 (Box 38)
  - Marzocca, Judith V., 1969 October 31 (Box 38)
  - Massena, Jan B., 1970 February 13 (Box 38)
  - Mathisen, Mathilda, 1967 September 20 (Box 38)
  - Mayer, Mary, 1966 May 13 (Box 38)
  - McCaffrey, Patricia, 1967 June 20 (Box 38)
  - McDermott, Maureen (Box 38)
  - McEvoy, Eileen M., 1964 April 27 (Box 38)
  - McGillen, Marilyn, 1967 June 2 (Box 38)
  - McGoldrick, Josephine C., 1963 February 4 (Box 38)
  - McGrath, Elizabeth C., 1967 November 15 (Box 38)
  - Mckeown, Mary Ann, 1967 May 26 (Box 38)
  - McKinley, Henry A., 1963 January 18 (Box 38)
  - McMurray, Ann W., 1962 November 30 (Box 38)
  - McSweeney, Maria Widman, 1963 August 2 (Box 38)
  - Meeks, Isollina T., 1964 January 3 (Box 38)
  - Melnick, Miriam, 1964 August 28 (Box 38)
  - Mendel, Harold, 1970 January 23 (Box 38)
  - Mercurio, John, 1969 November 4 (Box 38)